export default {
    HTML: [
        {
            "question": "Which of the following tag is used to mark",
            "options": [
                "Hyper Text Markup Language",
                "High Text Markup Language",
                "Hyper Tabular Markup Language",
                "None of these"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Hyper Text Markup Language",
            "selectedAnswer": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "a begining of paragraph ?",
            "options": [
                "<TD>",
                "<br>",
                "<P>",
                "<TR>"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "<P>",
            "selectedAnswer": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "From which tag descriptive list starts ?",
            "options": [
                "<LL>",
                "<DD>",
                "<DL>",
                "<DS> "
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "<DL>",
            "selectedAnswer": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "Correct HTML tag for the largest heading is",
            "options": [
                "<head>",
                "<h6>",
                "<heading>",
                "<h1>"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "<h1>",
            "selectedAnswer": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "The attribute of<form> tag",
            "options": [
                "Method",
                "Action",
                "Both(a) & (b)",
                "None of these"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Both(a) & (b)C",
            "selectedAnswer": ""
        },
    ],

    CSS: [
        {
            "question": "CSS full form is",
            "options": [
                "Cascading style sheet",
                "Css style sheet",
                "Content style sheet",
                "Country style sheet"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Cascading style sheet",
            "selectedAnswer": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "CSS is for",
            "options": [
                "Styling",
                "Designing",
                "Both (a)&(b)",
                "None of these"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Both (a)&(b)",
            "selectedAnswer": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "If we want to show an Arrow as cursor, then which value we will use?",
            "options": [
                "Pointer",
                "Default",
                "Arrow",
                "Ar "
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Default",
            "selectedAnswer": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "If we want to use a nice looking green dotted border around an image, which css property will we use?",
            "options": [
                "Border Color",
                "Border Decoration",
                "border-style",
                "border-line"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "border-style",
            "selectedAnswer": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "How can we write comment along with CSS code?",
            "options": [
                "/* a comment */",
                "// a comment //",
                "/ a comment /",
                "<' a comment'>"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "/* a comment */",
            "selectedAnswer": ""
        },
    ],
    Javascript: [
        {
            "question": "Which of the following is the correct syntax  to print a page using JavaScript?",
            "options": [
                "window.print();",
                "browser.print();",
                "navigator.print();",
                "document.print();"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "window.print();",
            "selectedAnswer": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "Which built-in method returns the characters in a string beginning at the specified location?",
            "options": [
                "substr()",
                "getSubstring()",
                "slice()",
                "None of the above."
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "substr()",
            "selectedAnswer": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following function of Boolean object returns the primitive value of the Boolean object?",
            "options": [
                "toSource()",
                "valueOf()",
                "toString()",
                "None of the above."
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "valueOf()",
            "selectedAnswer": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following function of String object is used to match a regular expression against a string?",
            "options": [
                "concat()",
                "match()",
                "search()",
                "replace()"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "match()",
            "selectedAnswer": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following function of String object creates an HTML anchor that is used as a hypertext target?",
            "options": [
                "anchor()",
                "link()",
                "blink()",
                "big()"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "anchor()",
            "selectedAnswer": ""
        },
    ],
}